I'm telling you it's coming strong and
ya os digo que se viene fuerte y
prepare yourselves for a few days of a lot of hate, be
preparad por unos días de mucho hate
prepared, be prepared it's going to be strong.
preparados preparados va a estar fuerte
I'm really into this thing about people
Yo de verdad el tema este de de la gente
supporting you and saying, Oh, I'm following you, I'm unfollowing you
el apoyo y decir Ay te sigo te dejo de
and there's also another
seguir y se viene además otro vídeo
surprise video coming from a character that every time I
sorpresa de un personaje de que cada vez
talk about him I get a lot of hate but I'm
que hablo de él me cae mucho hate per lo
going to do it anyway because you're
voy a hacer de todas maneras porque vais
really going to freak out about what I
de verdad a flipar de lo que me he
found out and it reveals once
enterado y pone al descubierto una vez
again that I was right it
más que yo tenía razón de verdad es que
's really always the same thing all the time, Herman,
siempre es todo el rato lo mismo herman
Herman You're going to freak out, freak out a lot You're going to
herman Vais a flipar flipar mucho Vais a
freak out with the videos that are coming guys they're going to
fpar con los videos que se vienen chicos
be very, very strong I'm not going to
van a estar muy muy muy fuertes no os
tell you who's coming but I'm telling you that they're
digo sobre quién viene pero os digo que
going to get really fired up and there's going to be a
se van a arder muchísimo y van a estar
lot of these clowns trying to
muchos de estos payasos intentando
fully defend this dirty character
defender a full a este sucio personaje
but what I have is more than evident and it's
pero lo que tengo es más que evidente y
an I told you again In Your Face
es un te lo dije otra vez In Your Face
again that video is going to be strong eh or it
de nuevo ese vídeo va a dar fuerte eh o
's German or it's German or it's German or it's
es Germán o es Germán o es Germán o es
German
Germán